don't know if they've done some of these
that some of these have popped into my
head and then popped out of that is
collection agencies yeah me so that
happened for a reason let's figure out
something around that so I mean it falls
into the last two etiquette guide more
lesson etiquette guide having am with
the law out what when I'm under
collections
what can the companies legally or not
make we do what could happen if I do if
I do paid that or don't pay debt what
kind of debt is good to pay not to pay
how does it affect my credit rating how
can i repair my credit rating finding
it's definitely I mean so a collection
you can see app would or I mean it falls
under the law I just feel like it's it's
too perfect I think we're calling right
then nothin I shared that with you
because I don't think that's something
was people share but when you're not
able to work because you have a
disability knows that up parent that can
bring me to my next stop baby bring me
to my next one so that was number
seventy-three couple the help with
collection and debt information